# NIKOLAI MAEV

Software Engineer

Site: <u>nickmaev.github.io</u> – <u>Email: trix.mnr@gmail.com</u> – <u>LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/sharpdev/</u>
Skype: <u>trix.mnr</u> – <u>Telegram: @trixon</u>

More than 10 years of experience in front- and back-end development with a vast array of knowledge in programming languages and tools. Development of SaaP and SaaS practice. Complex problem-solving practice. Good cooperation skills.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### ISDK, Senior Software Engineer, 2 years 1 month, 08/2020 – 09/2022

Full-stack software and database development from scratch using robust solutions. Query optimization. Technical interviews with potential customers as the company representative. Customer communication during development and presales. Working out the functional specifications. Task splitting and estimation. Integration of third-party platforms. Team management, staff training, code reviewing.

Stack: ASP.NET Core, PostgreSQL, MS SQL Server, Azure, Docker, Docker Compose, TypeScript, React, Redux, NodeJS, NextJS, Linux, Jenkins

## **StecPoint**, Software Engineer – Senior Software Engineer, 4 years 2 months, 05/2016 – 07/2020

Full-stack application development from scratch. Database design and optimization. Integration of third-party platforms. In-app purchase integration. Microservice development. Team management, staff training, code reviewing.

**Stack:** ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, SignalR, PostgreSQL, MS SQL Server, RabbitMQ, MS SQL Server, Razor, TypeScript, React, Redux, NodeJS

# **S4AB**, Junior Full Stack Developer – Software Engineer, 2 years 8 months, 07/2013 – 03/2016

Full-stack software development. Database development and query optimization. Design of small applications. Customer communication. Working out the functional specifications. Task splitting and estimation. jQuery plugin development.

**Stack:** ASP.NET MVC, SignalR, .NET Compact Framework, WinForms, PostgreSQL, MS SQL Server, Razor, JQuery

#### Freelance, Project Manager, Web Developer, Designer, 9 years, 2007 – 2016

Graphic design, promotional banner and logo design. Web design using vector, raster graphics and 3d modelling. Customer communication. Working out the functional specifications. Task splitting and estimation. Coding of the site design using Photoshop templates. Development and setting up online shops, forums and blogs. SEO, IT consulting.

**Stack:** PHP, WordPress, Joomla, Invision Power Board, Datalife Engine, JavaScript, jQuery Adobe/Macromedia Flash, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Cinema 4D

### **EDUCATION**

## SFEDU, Physics faculty, Russia, 5 years 10 months, 09/2007 – 07/2013

The specialist-level degree (eq. to Master's degree) in Radiophysics and Electronics.

## **KEY SKILLS**

- .NET (10y)
   PostgreSQL (6y)
   Docker (2y)
   English B2
- C# (10y)
   TypeScript (6y)
   Architecture Design (8y)
   Customer communication
- ASP.NET / Core (10y) React (6y) Jenkins (2y) Team management